WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Synced and corrected by Chitorafa
www.MY-SUBS.com
I want everything.
How did that son of
a bitch get the file?
I don't know.
He just gave me the copies.
Which you were going to publish.
A quarter to six!
Wake up, this ain't a vacation!
Ten minutes for
showering! Get up, people!
Get up, people! Up, I said!
- Gastn!
- Yasolrzano.
Miguel!
Cspedes, Cspedes.
Enrique!
Contreras Vidal.
Stand up.
Button up that shirt,
this ain't a party.
One more infraction,
and you'll spend a month in isolation.
Joaqun!
Guzmn Loera.
Silence!
Five minutes for breakfast.
One hour in the courtyard.
Eyes down.
Time to eat!
Walk.
Silence!
Four more, go.
Good night, Samuel.
Good night, professor.
Good night, Quique.
Good night, Professor Rubn.
Let's go, bitches.
A quarter to six!
Get up, this ain't a vacation!
Out of your cells!
Backs against the wall, eyes down.
Don't look!
Eyes down.
I heard you've been crying at night.
Answer me!
- No.
- No, what?
No, sir.
If I find out you're crying and
the other inmates can't sleep...
I'll make you cry for
a month in isolation.
- Got it?
- Yes, sir.
In this prison, you can only eat...
sleep...
and breathe.
Got it?
Yes, sir.
- Got it?
- Yes, sir!
My daughter told me she
had sent more letters.
They never gave them to me.
Sons of bitches.
Is security always this tight?
Everything is forbidden here, Chapo.
Even dying.
One line. Walk.
Empty your bag.
This stays here.
Take off your ring,
earrings, and glasses.
Go on.
Next.
- Take off your clothes.
- Excuse me?
Take off your clothes, please.
I've been searched twice.
It's procedure.
If you refuse, there's the door.
Stand there, please.
You can't bring blue pens.
Excuse me?
I said you can't bring blue pens.
Miss, I've done everything you've asked.
Let me see my son.
Time's up.
It's no coincidence
they're not letting you see your mom.
It's one of their games, Chapo.
They want to break you.
How are the kids, and how's Mom?
Everyone's fine. They
want to know how you are.
Any news on Too and Cho?
They're in another cell
block, but that's all I know.
Did you talk to the person
who promised me a bigger cage?
All I can do for you...
is move you to another penitentiary.
A friendlier one.
He will keep his promise,
but he says you have to wait.
How long?
Years. A few, at least.
JOURNALIST GABRIELA SAAVEDRA
MURDERED IN STRANGE CIRCUMSTANCES
Were you looking for this?
On your feet.
Let's take a walk.
Move.
Give me the keys.
Let's go.
What are you looking at?
Where?
Keep driving straight.
Has anyone made a friend here?
Do you mean the guards?
Yeah.
No.
They're watched all the time.
Their schedule changes
almost every single day.
What about the doctor?
The cooks?
No.
Same thing. The Lawyer
changes their schedule.
Who's the Lawyer?
She's in charge of the prison.
Wait, I thought De Tavira was in charge?
He only handles the
administrative stuff.
The Lawyer controls the daily stuff.
She's a criminal protected by the law.
Don't mess with her, Chapo.
All new houses have flaws.
I just need you to find
one so I can focus on it.
General Blanco's body
was found this morning.
He was one of the most important
men in the Federal Judicial Police
in our country. It is
believed to be a robbery.
The president is saddened
by this tragic event
and demands a thorough investigation.
General Blanco was my mentor, sir.
I'll help you find the
perpetrators, no matter what.
Thank you, Conrado. Let's
keep his family informed.
Of course.
A BRIEF AND MODERN HISTORY OF MEXICO
Hey.
What did you do to end up here?
I didn't do anything.
I'm innocent.
Me, too.
Ask my lawyer if you don't believe me.
And you, Professor? What did you do?
We blocked a road with my comrades.
We were protesting.
That's it?
The government considers
it a federal crime.
They treat us worse than
they treat you drug lords.
How long have you been here?
You really don't want to know, Chapo.
Any news?
The new house has got a fat cat.
Do you know him?
The fattest cat?
Yeah.
His kitten's been sick for some time.
They don't have money
to take her to the vet.
I can pay for your girl's treatment.
No dinner for Guzmn.
I need sleeping pills.
The doctor used to give us those.
But the Lawyer banned them.
We feel you, Chapo.
We can't sleep either.
But you're new here, Chapo.
With the punch you took,
you should ask see the doc.
Maybe he'll give you something.
If they catch you, they'll fuck you up.
Silence!
Good night, Samuel.
Good night, Professor.
Good night, Quique.
Good night, Professor Rubn.
Good night, Chapo.
Good night, Professor.
Out!
Out of your cells!
Get him out.
What is it?
Come on.
You can't have pills without
the doctor's authorization.
Who gave them to you?
You're going to the padded room.
No, please, no!
Please... beat me!
Take my food!
But, please, don't send me
there, I'm begging you, please...
I'm begging you, please!
Please, I'm begging you!
Don't do this!
Don't send me there!
Please, don't! No!
No! Not that place!
No, no, no!
Samuel.
What's the padded room?
You sent him there.
Son of a bitch!
Watch your mouth, asshole.
Rubn was brave enough to be quiet.
Don't you be the one who snitches.
They'll hear us.
Quique here is scared
out of his fucking mind.
What's the padded room, Quique?
The worst punishment, Chapo.
It's the end of the world.
- Lunch time.
- I'm not eating.
Lunch time.
I'm staying here.
Walk!
Get them out.
What's going on?
The Lawyer would like to remind you
you have to follow the rules here.
Not eating breaks the rules.
Quique.
Have you ever been where Rubn is?
Just a couple of days.
And I don't ever wanna go back.
If the rooms weren't padded,
one would hurt themselves
out of desperation.
My daughter got worse.
Mom.
My boy.
My boy...
Darling...
I'm sitting there.
I've been praying for you every day.
Look at you.
Don't worry, mom.
I'm tough as nails.
Chapo says you owe him.
Good night, Samuel.
Good night, Chapo.
Good night, Quique.
How long until Rubn is back?
A couple of nights, and
the punishment will be over.
Breakfast!
Rubn.
Professor.
You're loyal.
I owe you.
Rubn.
Professor.
What are you doing?
- Professor.
- What are you doing?
- He's hanging himself!
Let me die. Let me die.
Put him back in his cell.
Watch him 24/7. I don't want
him doing something stupid.
Let me die...
Please...
Take him to the doctor.
Help him like I helped
your daughter, asshole!
Open up.
You're such a tough guy...
Take him to isolation.
Synced and corrected by Chitorafa
www.MY-SUBS.com
Subtitle translation
by Mara Pa Rebussone